{
    "subject": "resource/Adolph_Menzel",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Adolph_Menzel",
    "human_readable": "Adolph Menzel is primarily about the topic of Adolph Menzel.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9271414279937744,
            "question": "What subjects did Adolph Menzel primarily focus on in his work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8626981973648071,
            "question": "Who was Adolph Menzel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7928822040557861,
            "question": "What artistic movement is Adolph Menzel associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7713022232055664,
            "question": "What techniques was Adolph Menzel known for using?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.644585132598877,
            "question": "What inspired Adolph Menzel's artwork?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6329132914543152,
            "question": "What are some of Adolph Menzel's most famous works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6242745518684387,
            "question": "What is the legacy of Adolph Menzel in art history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5665176510810852,
            "question": "How is Adolph Menzel's art viewed today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47630372643470764,
            "question": "Where did Adolph Menzel live and work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3017616868019104,
            "question": "Did Adolph Menzel receive any recognition for his work during his lifetime?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Adolph Menzel is primarily about the topic of Adolph Menzel.",
            "html": "dbpedia_665_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Adolph Menzel live and work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_665_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is Adolph Menzel's art viewed today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_665_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the legacy of Adolph Menzel in art history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_665_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_665_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_665_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_665_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_665_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_665_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_665_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_665_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_665_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_665_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_665_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The information provided does not suggest that all the documents are primarily about the topic of Adolph Menzel. While some documents (e.g., file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_665/re-ranker-msmarco/23.txt) focus on him, others provide more general information about realism as an art movement or trivia and fun facts about his life and career. Therefore, the triple is not supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Adolph Menzel, his life, works, and artistic style. Therefore, the statement \"Adolph Menzel is primarily about the topic of Adolph Menzel\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "It's too narrow a scope. \n\nThe context information suggests that Adolph Menzel was an artist with a broad range of subject matter and artistic expression, not just focused on one topic. His work includes history painting, contemporary events, drawings, etchings, paintings, landscapes, genre paintings, self-portraits, and more, indicating a diverse range of interests and themes.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}